# MARCUS HALL

## Oracle certified Full stack Developer

+1-234-253-6506 @ danette.eastwood@gmail.com 

## **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Developer with over 10 years of experience in Java/JS, Angular, Vue, React, Python, NumPy, SciPy, Scikit-learn. Led development of \$500K research project which was deemed a "gold standard" by the client. Increased client's revenue 2-fold after fine-tuning Al/ML-based algorithms. Well-acquainted with HR methodologies.

#### **EDUCATION**

M.S. in Computer Science

2008 - 2009

Stanford Unversity

Palo Alto, CA

GPA 3.9 / 4.0

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Senior Full stack Developer

2018 - Present

**Boyle** 

San Fransisco, CA

Boyle is an international Technology and Management Consulting Group with a rapid pace development and innovative solutions for demanding projects. I work as a full-stack developer here, responsible for building, deploying and maintaining internal web applications.

- Hired, trained and leading an Agile team of 7 full-stack developers
- Developed indexed database architecture using SQL procedures and triggers for 10 different applications
- Worked with Core Java to develop automated solutions to include web interfaces using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Web services
- Worked with a committee of 6 members to organise fun-activities for the employees

## Full Stack Developer

2013 - 2018

Lauzon

San Fransisco, CA

Lauzon is a universal digital loyalty program that offers unique and fun rewards at the places you love.

- Hired, trained and lead Agile team of 7 full-stack developers
- Simultaneously created & maintained scheduled jobs in SQL Server for space maintenance and daily backups of system and user databases for 10 clients
- Increased company revenue by 30% within 2 months after developing and implementing business logic for over 20 features
- Designed and Developed UI design for over 15 clients using CSS, HTML, ASP.NET, Vue, and React; websites scoring over 85 on Lighthouse

## Solution Architect

2010 - 2013

## **Keeling Group**

Palo Alto, CA

Keeling Group is a leading Digital Product Studio in California, helping companies to thrive on mobile apps, the web, VR/AR and IoT.

- Shortened project timeline by 14 months for company's largest customer by managing relationship with 3rd party vendors, saving over \$800K
- Led development of \$500K research project which was deemed a "gold standard" by the
- Fine-tuned and developed Al/ML-based algorithms based on the results with Scikit-learn, increasing revenue 2-fold
- Performed Web Scraping over a catalog of 100K+ school supply products using mainly NodeJS and MongoDB; completed in 1 month

## **SKILLS**

Client-Side

HTML · CSS · JS · Angular · React · Vue ·

Redux · TypeScript · Backbone ·

Bootstrap

Server-side

Python · NumPy · SciPy · Scikit-learn ·

Keras · Eli5 · TensorFlow · MySQL ·

NodeJS · Redis · AWS · MongoDB · Spark · HTTP/2

**Development & Operations** 

JUnit · NUnit · PyUnit · TestCafe · Mocha ·

Jest · Scrum · Agile · GIT · Azure DevOps

## **PROJECTS**

#### **OpenFlow based Firewall**

08/2012 - 12/2013

Palo Alto, CA

OpenFlow protocol-based proactive Firewall in Python and NodeJS.

- Configured static rules using MD-SAL
- Engineered proactive rule evaluation system at OSI layer 7 using POX controller
- Provided flexibility to configure rule using centralised NodeJS based GUI

https://github.com/danette.east/OpenFlow-Firewall

## **STRENGTHS**

## Team Leadership

Introduction to Leadership course by Harvard

## Communication

Attended a Communication course at Stanford.